God dammit!
時間軸     紫夏  大蔥  啾啾啾  小式
Holy shit, man!
上帝啊
Watch where you're going.
看著點路
What the fuck?
搞什么
Jesus Christ.
上帝啊
Did you make this?
這是你做的嗎
This is unbelievable.
真是難以置信
Oh my God, dude.
天啊  哥們
This looks so real.
看上去好逼真
Dot, look at this thing.
多多  你看看
Don't call me Dot.
別叫我多多
Wait a second.
等等
What are you doing right now?
你現在要去做什么
I know, I know that's a weird thing to ask a stranger, but, uh,
我知道這么貿然問陌生人不好  但是
we're on our way to this party,
我們正要去一個派對
and it's gonna be outrageously cool
那里會非常非常酷
and, like, super sick,
超級牛逼
and I was kind of hoping we can make a big entrance
我本來想我們能搞個隆重登場
at this thing, but, um,
之類的  但是
as you can see...
如你所見
we look pathetic, so...
我們看上去很可悲  所以
I got off work, like, 30 minutes ago, so...
我大概30分鐘前剛下班吧  所以
Still could have made an effort, Nick.
你還是能努力努力的  尼克
- Well, I... - What are you supposed to be?
-我...  -你想扮成什么
- What are you dressed as? - This is steampunk.
-你想扮成什么  -這是蒸汽朋克
- This and... - Goggles?
-這和...  -護目鏡
You're dressed as goggles?
你要打扮成護目鏡嗎
I'm sorry, who are you?
抱歉  你是誰
Oh, shit, sorry, Alan Morgan Adams
該死  抱歉  艾倫·摩根·亞當斯
of the Massachusetts Morgan Adamses.
就是馬薩諸塞州的那個摩根亞當斯[地名]
Hey, hey, buddy,
伙計
Where are we goin'?
要去哪里呢
Are you, like, uh,
你是
the British American Psycho or something?
英國美國瘋子之類的嗎
Whoa, Dorothy.
多蘿西
Sorry, you gotta forgive her.
抱歉  請原諒她
She's from Westlake.
她來自韋斯特萊克
We're still workin' on her manners.
我們還在教她怎么禮貌待人
We're kind of a...
我們有點...
My Fair Lady type of deal.
像《窈窕淑女》那一套
He's the, uh, self-important drunk perv
他是那個自命不凡的醉鬼
who thinks that he's a big deal,
覺得自己很了不起
and I'm just the bad ass everyone wants to hang out with.
而我就是那個誰都想上的小太妹
So is this, like, your...
這是你的...
latest victim or something?
上一名被害人之類的嗎
Yes, for now.
暫時算是
Okay, dude, dude, dude, dude.
哥們  哥們  哥們
Uh, you gotta come with us.
你得跟我們來
What can I say
我要怎么說
that is gonna get you there?
才能勸得動你
There's gonna be an open bar.
那里有個免費酒吧
Does that do anything for you?
你覺得怎么樣
There's gonna be outrageously hot chicks,
那里會有很多辣妞
like crazy hot chicks.
真的很辣
- Fucking gag me. - Okay, okay.
-笑死我了  -好吧
Everybody is gonna be there, man.
所有人都會去哪里的  伙計
I can assure you
我保證
that the party we're going to
我們要去的這個派對
is a million times cooler
比你現在要去的
than the party you were going to.
好上百萬倍
My buddy Jack,
我哥們杰克
he, uh, he's the host.
他是主辦的
He always does this, like,
他經常
grand arrival,
隆重登場
and everyone flips out about his costume, but this thing,
大家都會吹他的打扮  但這個
this is gonna blow his cock off.
這絕對讓他望塵莫及
Look, uh, someone slashed my tires,
聽著  有人劃破了我的輪胎
and I really need...
我真的需要...
You need a ride.
你需要搭車
Done.
沒問題
That we can do.
我們能幫你
We can get you a ride, man.
我們能載你一程  伙計
Consider it done.
沒問題
Please walk away.
請你讓開
Yeah, no, there's...
不  你...
there's no way you're gonna get a cab
你不可能拖著這玩意
with this thing, dude, so...
打到車的  哥們
He's right, that's a good point, Nick.
他說得對  很有道理  尼克
Thank you for finally making a contribution.
謝謝你終于派上了點用場
No one's gonna let you in the back of a cab
沒人會讓你帶著這東西
with this thing, you'll make a mess.
上出租車的  那會一團糟
Come with us for one drink.
跟我們去喝一杯
Just one drink, you walk right back out,
就一杯  你就能離開
you're out on the streets,
回到大街上
you're killin' all your victims in no time.
繼續殺死你的受害者
You know what?
你知道嗎
That actually sounds like a really good idea.
這主意聽上去還真的不錯
Let's do it.
就這樣吧
What?
什么
I can't believe that worked.
真不敢相信這樣就行了
Wow, I did not see that coming.
我還真沒想到
It's the best night of my life.
這簡直是我的巔峰之夜
This is exciting.
真是太棒了
What an exciting turn of events.
多么棒的轉折
Lift with your legs, Nick.
好好幫忙抬著  尼克
There's four of us.
我們有四個人呢
If we all just, um...
如果我們能一起...
Oh my gosh.
上帝啊
Slashed your tires, huh?
刮輪胎的
Bunch of fuckin' savages in this town.
這城里真是一群變態
Put your back into it, Nick.
好好抬著  尼克
It's pretty heavy.
很重呢
Oh yeah, here we go!
我們到了
This way, this way, come on!
這邊  這邊  來
Here we go again!
我們又來了
That ought to be good.
絕對會很棒
Prop him up there.
把他放在那里
Do not move, okay?
別動  好嗎
Don't move, I'm gonna go find Jack.
別動  我去找尼克
Especially this guy.
特別是這個
Everybody raise your hands!
大家嗨起來
Where is this guy?
這家伙去哪里了
Girls and boys,
帥哥美女們
queer gender friends,
還有變性的朋友們
please turn your eyes to the dance floor
請將你們的目光投向舞池中央
and welcome your host,
歡迎派對主人
Jack Baker,
杰克·貝克
Monster Maker!
怪獸制造者
Oh, shit.
該死
Hello Alan.
你好  艾倫
Unreal.
絕了
Dalmore neat, double.
純達爾摩  雙倍
Here.
給
Here, want it?
給  要嗎
Excuse me.
讓一下
Your costume is...
你的裝扮真是...
brilliant.
天才
It's not a costume.
這不是裝扮
Uh, yeah, more of a prop, I guess, right?
更應該說是戲服吧
The whole package really works.
這一套效果很棒
The suit, the blood.
西裝  血跡
Maggie.
我叫瑪姬
Let them eat cake.
讓他們吃蛋糕吧
She never said that.
她沒有這么說過
You know, Marie Antoinette,
瑪麗亞·安東尼特
she never actually said,
她其實從來沒有說過
"Let them eat cake."
"讓他們吃蛋糕吧"
It was just a thing that French like to attribute
這只是法國人用來
to every foreign queen they didn't like the look of.
抹黑他們不喜歡的外來皇后的
I mean, when things go wrong,
出了什么差錯
why blame the king when you can blame his bitch of a wife?
明明能怪國王的賤皇后  為什么要怪國王呢
She's a very meaningful woman, I think.
我覺得她是一名非常有內涵的女性
Um, famous,
非常著名
but as a caricature that confirms men's prejudices against women
也是對男性對女性偏見的一種諷刺
frivolous, ditzy,
輕浮  輕佻
obsessed with buying shoes,
喜歡買鞋子
silly, pretty, tragic little bonbon
愚蠢  美麗  悲劇的小可憐
good for porn, good for scorn,
容易色情  容易藐視
nothing in between.
別的就沒了
Well, you have really thought about your costume.
你對你的裝扮還真是有很多想法
Says the guy dragging a corpse around?
你拖著一具尸體到處跑也好意思說我
Did you not come here with friends, Maggie?
你沒有和什么朋友一起來嗎  瑪姬
Just me.
我一個人
I hesitated to come, but tonight felt like
我本來也在猶豫  但是今晚
the kind of night something might happen.
總覺得冥冥之中會發生什么事
Well, you certainly make that costume work.
你挑的衣服的確很不錯
A girl is expected to dress a little provocatively
一個女孩子被邀請到這種派對時
when she's invited to one of these parties.
就是約定俗成地要打扮得奔放一點
Why would a girl want to be
為什么女孩子會想要
invited to one of these parties?
被邀請到這種派對
Oh, I don't know,
我不知道
one of these parties,
這種派對
one of these clubs,
這種俱樂部
one of these jobs.
這種工作
It might be 230 years since the French Revolution,
法國革命已經過去了230年了
but boys still need the illusion
但男孩子們還是想看到
of silly, tragic little bonbons.
愚蠢的悲劇的小可憐
Maybe that's not your problem.
也許那不是你的問題
Maybe that's obviously occurred to me before,
也許我本來就很清楚這一點
and I don't need it mansplained to me by a stranger.
不需要一個陌生人來給我解釋
So how long did it take you to stuff it?
你花了多久塞東西進去的
You don't stuff it, it's more of, um...roll,
不是塞的  更應該說是  卷起阿貍
like a...pig in blanket.
就像...用毯子包豬
Those are harder to roll cleanly than they look.
看起來應該很難卷好
It gets easier every time you do it.
熟能生巧
I do it this way every Halloween.
我每年萬圣節都會做一次
You have to be a lot more careful disposing of a dead body
在普通的晚上拋尸
on a normal evening.
得更小心
Right.
好吧
Would you like me to, uh...
你想讓我...
let you in on something?
給你科普一下嗎
People think that killing is the hard part.
人們總認為殺人是最難的
They also assume that the necessary next step
他們還認為下一步必須要做的是
is hiding the evidence,
隱藏證據
but it's not.
但其實不是
You can't do it, not reliably.
你隱藏不了  這不可靠
You have to come up with an alternative story
你得想點別的說法
for how this person died.
編這個人的死因
Needs its own narrative, its own evidence,
需要有專門的手法  專門的證據
its own culprit.
專門的犯人
Takes more effort,
需要花更大的力氣
but if you can do it correctly,
但如果你能處理得當
it works.
就能成功
You can do anything,
你什么都能做到
as long as you don't give people the time to decide
只要你別給人足夠的時間
it's something different from what you're telling them it is.
發現其實和你告訴他們的有出入
And that...is what makes this...
這就是為什么...這行
special.
這么特殊
That makes sense.
有道理
I'm not sure it all comes across in the costume, but...
我也不確定你這裝扮是不是這意思  不過
Okay, dude, a toast to every Friday the 13th movie.
哥們  敬電影《黑色星期五》
Let's do this.
來吧
Friday the 13th.
《黑色星期五》
Friday the 13th Part 2. Part 2.
《黑色星期五2》
"Midway upon life's journey,
"人生路過半
I found myself within a forest dark."
我發現自己在黑暗的森林中"
"For the straightforward path had been lost."
"面前的路通往迷途"
Hell's empty and all the devils are here.
地獄空蕩蕩  惡魔在人間
Jason Takes Manhattan.
《黑色星期五8》
Are you leaving?
你要走了嗎
I've been promised a ride to work.
有人答應我要送我去工作
You came with that guy Alan, right?
你跟那個叫艾倫的人一起來的吧
He's friends with Jack.
他是杰克的工作
I work for Jack.
字幕
Um, he's designing this horror virtual reality thing,
他在設計什么虛擬恐怖現實什么的
and I'm the coder who has to do all the damn work.
我是干活的程序員
It's really...
那些活...
really makes you feel good about those student loan debts.
讓你覺得你自己的學生貸款可真值
Worth it.
太值了
Um, I can, uh,
我可以
get you a car and drive you.
給你搞輛車  送你去
Is anybody expecting you home tonight, Maggie?
今晚有人在等你回家嗎  瑪姬
Not a soul.
完全沒有
Well, all right then.
那好吧
I'll be right back.
我馬上回來
Hey, what's up, girl?
你好啊  妹子
Hey, sexual harassment is a crime, shithead.
性騷擾是犯罪  混蛋
- Whatever. - Criminal!
-隨便了  -罪犯
Uh, we're almost ready.
快準備好了
I just...the body thing is huge.
我只是...這尸體太重了
I was just...figured we could use
我只是...我們可能需要
some help getting it downstairs.
找人幫忙抬下樓
There is no "We."
沒有什么"我們"
What?
怎么了
I agreed to one drink. I've had three.
我只同意喝一杯  我都喝了三倍了
Car, now.
車
- Dude, chill. - What, no.
-哥們  但丁  -別這樣
I already told Maggie you can borrow my car.
我已經告訴瑪姬你能借我的車了
Now come on!
淡定點
Enjoy yourself for a bit, huh?
能不能放松點
Take me to your car now
帶我上你的車
or I will kill you at your own party.
不然我就在你的派對上把你殺了
You really got this killer thing down.
你真的很像一個殺手
You nailed it.
你做得很棒
I like it.
我喜歡
All right, all right.
好吧  好吧
I'll take you downstairs.
我帶你下樓
But first, shots!
但首先  抽幾口
Finally we get to the good shit.
終于有好東西了
Dude, he never lets anyone in there.
哥們  他從來不放任何人進去的
This night's gonna be epic. Okay?
今天晚上絕對史無前例
Hey, don't break anything.
別弄壞什么東西了
Come on, one shot won't kill you.
來吧  抽一點死不了
Every single one of those
每一件
literally cost thousands of dollars.
都要好幾千呢
Yeah, I got money
對  我有錢
and talent.
還有才
So I'm gonna need those car keys now.
我現在就需要車鑰匙
Yeah, we should probably get back to the party.
對  我們也許該回到派對上去了
Aw, not yet, guys.
別急  伙計們
Come on.
來吧
Hey, where are you going in such a hurry anyway?
你到底這么急著去哪里
Can we come?
我們能去嗎
Yo, dude,
哥們
this is your party.
這是你的派對
You got Sasha Grey DJing.
薩沙·格雷是你的DJ
You can't leave...he can't leave the party.
你不能離開...他不能離開排隊
I can do whatever I want.
我想干什么就干什么
Guys, this...this is what tonight is all about.
伙計們  這就是今晚的重點
All Hallow's Eve,
萬圣節前夕
the night we put our masks on
我們戴上面具
and let our dark, unpredictable sides fly.
放飛我們黑暗  未知的一面
This guy, man, look at him.
這家伙  伙計  看看他
The costume, woo!
這裝扮
The performance.
這表演
I'm telling you, bro,
我告訴你  兄弟
next level commitment.
這簡直上了一個檔次
Think about it, guys.
伙計們  你們想想
How do we usually end the night?
我們這一晚一般都是怎么結束的
Me, sittin' at home
我  坐在家里
watching Plan 9 from Outer Space,
看《外部空間》的《第九計劃》
mixing cocktails,
調雞尾酒
sending unsolicited dick pics to Dorothy.
給多蘿西轟炸屌照
Or, guys, we keep the party goin', right?
或者  伙計們  我們可以把派對繼續下去
Keep the party goin',
把派對繼續下去
lookin' for somebody,
找個人
like this guy right here.
就像這位家伙
I don't know what's goin' down tonight,
我不知道今晚是怎么回事
but I am feeling so,
但我感覺
what's the word? Alive.
怎么說來著  很有活力
I'm feelin' so alive right now, guys.
我感覺現在很有活力  伙計們
Yeah, he, um...
他...
he occasionally, uh...
他偶爾
does that.
是會這樣
Wait.
等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等  等等  等等
This animatronic too?
還有動畫效果
Woo, that is amazing!
真是太棒了
Give it a kick, it'll stop.
給他一腳  就會停下來了
You can do better than that.
你可以做得更好
Oh, really?
真的嗎
All right.
好吧
Shit!
該死
Did I fix it?
我修好了嗎
I don't know.
我不知道
Did you?
修好了嗎
Jesus!
上帝啊
Shit! That's an actual body!
該死  那是一具真的尸體
That's an actual body.
那是一具真的尸體
Okay, okay, okay.
好吧  好吧
That's a dead person for real.
那真的是一個死人
Put your fucking hands down.
把你的手放下來
Sorry.
抱歉
Ugh, accepting a ride from strangers
搭陌生人的車
is always such a bad idea.
總是一個糟糕的主意
So, uh...
那么
did you kill this guy?
你殺了這個人嗎
Well, he wasn't dead a minute ago.
他一分鐘前還沒死
If he is now, then technically
如果他現在死了  那嚴格來說
you killed him.
是你殺了他
Are you, uh, are you a hitman
你  你是個殺手
or something, or...
之類的嗎  還是...
Jesus Christ, man.
上帝啊  伙計
You can't just kill people!
你不能就這么殺人
Course you can.
當然可以
Oh shit!
該死
Oh shit, man!
該死  伙計
I was just on VentureBeat's list of 40 under 40,
我才剛上了科技網《40名40以下成功人士》榜
I can't die like this!
我不能就這么死了
Okay, what's your name?
好吧  你叫什么名字
It's Jack, right?
杰克  對吧
And what do you do, Jack?
你是干什么的  杰克
Uh, I'm an artist.
我是一名藝術家
I have a trust fund, okay?
我有信托基金  好嗎
Please!
保妥
And would you define yourself as "Sane"?
你覺得你自己是"理智"的嗎
I...I...
我...我...
Anything you do other than
你所做的除了
eat, sleep, shit, fuck, and kill
吃飯  睡覺  拉屎  做愛和殺戮以外的事
is a symptom of insanity.
都是瘋狂的標志
You see, there was a point
在人類進化的
during human evolution where something,
過程中
some neuron pathway misfired,
出了一些神經上的分叉
and we all became self-ware.
我們自我的意識覺醒
That is to say, we became insane.
也就是說  我們變得瘋狂
We are balls of flesh and bone
我們就是一團血肉
on a rock of ice
棲息在冰層上
spinning through a dark, random universe
在黑暗的宇宙中無序地轉動
designed only to survive,
唯一的目的就是生存
but then something happened in our DNA
但是然后我們基因中發生了某種變化
where we went, "Hey, wait, wait, wait.
我們想  "等等  等等
What if I matter?
萬一我很重要呢
What if it's all about me?"
萬一這一切都是因為我呢"
Did you ever watch those, um...
你們有沒有看過
the David Attenborough shows?
大衛·愛丁保羅夫的節目
They're magnificent, right?
很棒吧
Full of death.
充滿了死亡
And yet in a way, it makes sense.
但不知為何  看起來很合理
And then you try and watch the news and it's crazy.
然后你看新聞  就覺得很瘋狂
There's no sense at all.
完全沒有道理
And I will answer that other question for you.
然后我還有另一個問題的答案
Does a crazy person know they're crazy?
瘋了的人知道自己瘋了嗎
Yes, it's called a conscience.
知道  這叫良知
Jiminy Cricket,
吉姆尼·克里克特
that's just the part of our brains
那只是我們的大腦
screaming at the psychic tear
因為被分裂成我們的本我和
caused by the gulf between what we are
我們所假裝成的樣子
and what we pretend to be.
而在淚水中發出的尖叫
You think the world needs your doodles, artist?
你覺得世界需要你的涂鴉嗎  藝術家
There's no art in the natural world.
自然界中沒有藝術
There is murder.
只有謀殺
Do you really think
你真的覺得
it made a difference to the world
他生或死對自然界來說
if he lived or died?
有什么區別嗎
That was the most amazing thing i've ever heard.
這簡直是我挺過最動聽的話
Do you know how often
你知道我有多
I've wanted to do that to somebody?
經常想要這么做嗎
That's a...
那真是...
Car keys, now.
車鑰匙  快點
Jack, he's gonna fucking kill us.
杰克  他會把我們都殺了
He is right.
他說得對
However, if you agree to help me,
不管怎樣  如果你答應幫我
I promise I'll make it quick.
我保證會趕緊完事
Top drawer.
最上面的抽屜
You.
你
Close the drawer.
關上抽屜
What the hell was that?
那是怎么回事
I rigged it as an escape route.
我改裝成用來逃生的
I thought it would be a fun way to impress girls.
我本來想靠這個泡妹子
That is so rapey.
真是太遜了
Oh my God!
天啊
Go, go, go, go.
走走走
- Jack, Jack, what are you - Jack!
-杰克  杰克  你...  -杰克
Stop, stop the music!
停  停下音樂
Please, somebody call the police!
拜托快報警
One of my guests is trying to kill us!
有一名客人要殺了我們
What the fuck?
搞什么
Come on!
快走
Jesus Christ.
上帝啊
Go, go, go.
快走  快走
I didn't know about the drawer, I swear.
我不知道抽屜的事  我發誓
What's wrong with you?
你怎么回事
I know Jack.
我了解杰克
If there's a shortcut way out of this room,
如果有捷徑能離開這個房間
it's gonna be revealed by some smug, nerdy
肯定能通過某些低劣  下流
inside joke onanism.
無聊的機關找到
I can figure it out.
我能找出來
Thank you.
謝謝你
Hurry up, come on!
快點  快點
Guys, what the hell are we doing, huh?
伙計們  我們在干什么
But why did we take this thing?
我們為什么要帶走這玩意
Dude, this thing is a person.
哥們  這玩意是個人
Dude, there's probably a reward out on this guy.
哥們  舉報這家伙可能有獎賞
- What? - What?
-什么  -什么
There's always a reward when you turn in a murderer.
舉報一名殺人犯總是會有獎賞的
They're gonna give us a pile of money.
他們會給我們一筆錢
Everyone's gonna love us.
人人都會愛我們
We're gonna be heroes!
我們就會成為英雄
Oh my, what are you,
天啊  你是什么東西啊
Dog the Bounty Hunter?
賞金獵人狗嗎
Is that not why you picked it up?
你不是因為這個才一起搬這玩意的嗎
Uh, it is not an it,
這不是"玩意"
it is a person
這是一個人
that might still be alive.
可能還活著
Yeah, but that guy's gonna want him - back.
好吧  但那個人可能想把他要回去
Wait.
等等
Why is this suddenly our problem?
這為什么突然變成我們的問題了
Okay.
好吧
We're gonna give him to the cops
我們要把他交給警察
and then he stops being our problem. Okay?
然后他就和我們沒關系了  好嗎
Jack, keys?
杰克  鑰匙呢
What?
什么
You were giving that guy a ride.
你本來要載那家伙一程的
Yeah, but he went all psycho
是啊  但是他瘋了
before I could grab the keys.
我都沒來得及拿鑰匙
Then why the fuck are we down here?
那我們為什么要下來這里
I thought you guys drove!
我以為你們開車來的
Oh my God!
天啊
Nick drove us, you jackass.
尼克開車載我們來的  混蛋
He parked three blocks away.
他停在三個街區外了
Okay, so where are his keys?
那他的鑰匙在哪里
Aw, shit.
該死
He wasn't wrong about you, was he?
他對你的揣測沒錯  對嗎
You are a hitman, right?
你的確是個殺手
Could be in here for a really long time, you know?
我們可是可能在這里關上很久的
- Dude, Uber, right? - Yes.
-哥們  優步  -對
- Yes. - Are you kidding me?
-沒錯  -你在開玩笑嗎
Call 911.
報警
Okay, uh...
好吧
Shit, I left my phone upstairs.
該死  我把手機丟在樓上了
Oh my God, okay, fine.
天啊  好吧
I'll get the car.
我來轎車
No one is gonna let us
沒有人會讓我們
get into the car with a body.
帶著尸體上車的
No, no, they can be heroes with us.
不  他們能和我們一起當英雄
Are you serious?
你是認真的嗎
Look, call the cops.
報警
Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等  等等
When we came in here,
我們來的時候
there were cops outside.
外面就有警察
Uh, yes, uh, go, go now.
對  去  快去
Go.
快去
What did you say you wanted, Randy?
你說你想要什么來著  蘭迪
A cinnamon raisin bagel, toasted, half butter--half
肉桂葡萄干百吉餅  半黃油  半
otherwise it gets all drippy.
不然會滴下來
Two creams, two sugars in the coffee.
咖啡加兩份奶  兩份糖
Oh, what the hell is this?
這是怎么回事
Central, this is Unit 1-Alpha-7-8.
調度中心  這里是1A78小隊
Think I got another drunk and disorderly.
我這應該又有一個酒后鬧事的
He's possibly on drugs.
他可能是吸毒了
- Please! - Definitely on drugs.
-拜托  -絕對嗑藥了
Please, I need you.
拜托  我需要你
Hey, what the hell are you doin'?
你在干什么
Jesus Christ, I'm so happy to see you.
天啊  見到你真是太好了
Step back from the window.
離車窗遠一點
Now.
快點
Sir, um,
長官
my friends, they're down there,
我的朋友們都在那邊
and in the building over there.
都在那邊的樓里
We--we need--we need you to come.
我們  我們需要你跟我來
I need you to come with me, please.
我需要你跟我來  拜托
Hey West, I got a couple of drunks to deal with.
威斯特  我這里有幾個醉鬼
You need me to come back?
要我回來嗎
Nah, I got it.
不用  我可以的
All right, son.
好吧  孩子
Show me.
帶我去吧
Come on, come on, come on!
快點快點快點
Please hurry up, come on!
拜托快點
He's coming back!
他要回來了
Okay.
好吧
No...
不
Count of Monte Cristo.
《基督山伯爵》
Classic prison escape scene.
經典越獄用具
Code is probably the release date
密碼很可能是《驅魔人》
for The Exorcist or THX1138 or...
或者《五百年后》的發行日期
We work pretty well together.
我們合作得很愉快啊
There is no "We."
沒有什么"我們"
Guys!
伙計們
- Oh, yes! - Yes, yes, yes!
-太好了  -太好了  太好了
Yes!
太好了
Oh, thank God.
謝天謝地
Come on, guys.
拜托  伙計們
Look, I know it's Halloween and everything,
我知道現在是萬圣節
but you could really scare the hell
但是這玩意還是能
out of somebody with this thing.
把人嚇出老命
Oh, no, no, please, uh, we need your help.
不不不  拜托  我們需要你的幫助
Stay where you are, miss.
別過來  女士
Uh, officer, please
警官  拜托
Hey, stay where you are!
別過來
No, no, no, please,
不不不  拜托
you don't understand.
你不明白
Command, I got a code 6A,
指揮部  有人襲警
three intoxicated persons, one hysterical female.
三名吸毒者  一名精神崩潰的女性
You fucking asshole!
你這個混蛋
Stand down!
后退
Female is possibly armed.
女性可能持有武器
Stand down from what, you fucking moron?
后退什么  你這個白癡
Someone is dead here
有人死了
and we need your help.
我們需要你的幫助
Whoa, whoa, whoa, okay, okay.
好了  好了
It's gettin' away from us here.
越扯越遠了
I know this doesn't look good.
我知道這看上去不大妙
Just listen to me. My name is Alan Morgan Adams.
聽我說  我叫艾倫·摩根·亞當斯
Of the Massachusetts Morgan Adamses.
馬薩諸塞州的那個摩根亞當斯
Okay, uh, we are not the ones you're looking for.
你要抓的不是我們
He is going to be here any fucking second,
他馬上就會到這里來
No, freeze right now!
不  不許動
No, wait!
不  等等
Look, it's a real person.
看  這是個真人
Wait, is that who I think it is?
等等  這是我以為的那個人嗎
He's famous.
他很有名
And rich.
還很有錢
And beautiful.
還很漂亮
All right, so wait, just walk
好吧  等等  再跟我
walk me through all this again.
跟我說一遍是怎么回事
No, no, you need to call for backup right now
不  你得趕緊呼叫增援
or we are all going to die.
不然我們都得死
You tell me who did this.
告訴我是誰干的
Guys.
伙計們
He did it.
是他干的
Hey you, stop right there!
你給我站住
- Oh, shit. - Freeze!
-該死  -不許動
Just shoot the bastard!
開槍打那個混蛋
Miss, you stay back,
小姐  后退
you let me take care of this.
交給我來處理
Now this is your last warning.
這是給你的最后一次警告
What are you doing?
你在干什么
Do you really think Chief Wiggum's
你覺得這位威格姆隊長[動畫人物]
gonna save the day?
能拯救世界嗎
Good point.
說得好
Put your hands where I can see them.
把手舉到我看得到的地方
I said put your hands up!
我說舉起手來
Ooh, wait.
等等
Oh God...
天啊
Hey, stop!
站住
Come on, stop!
喂  站住
Don't go anywhere!
別跑
You stop right now!
你們給我站住
What the hell!
搞什么
I...
我...
Hey Randy.
蘭迪
They're out of cinnamon raisin, buddy.
沒有肉桂葡萄干百吉餅  哥們
Can you believe that?
你敢信嗎
You're a murderer, they're thieves,
你是殺人犯  他們是小偷
I'm the one who gets shot.
結果中槍的是我
Okay, I can find them.
好吧  我能找到他們
I just need a computer.
我只需要一臺電腦
If they have a cell phone,
如果他們有手機
I can track them.
我就能追蹤他們
A flesh wound.
新鮮的傷口
Talk and walk.
邊走邊說
Guys, what the fuck are we gonna do now?
伙計們  我們現在要怎么辦
Oh my God, I've never been
天啊  我從來沒有
this close to a famous person before.
這么接近過名人
Dude, put that thing down, man!
哥們  放下
No, we're not putting him down!
不  我們不放
Are you kidding me?
你開什么玩笑
You guys know who this is
你們都知道他是誰
and we get to be the ones that rescued him.
我們可是拯救他的人
Wait a second.
等等
Hey, you know what?
你知道嗎
We're not rescuing him
我們不能救他
because he's dead!
因為他死了
Okay, whatever.
好吧  隨便吧
We need to get off the street, okay?
我們不能走大路
And why couldn't he just kill,
他為什么不殺
like, Elijah Wood or someone small?
伊利亞·伍德之類名氣小點的人呢
We could just take that.
我們可以推走這個
Yeah, you want to rip off a homeless guy?
對  你想搶一個流浪漢嗎
Do you want to shoot a puppy
你要不要順便
while we're at it too, hmm?
弄死一只小狗
Oh, I'm sorry, would you rather
抱歉  難道你更希望
that the fucking psychopath catches up with us, Dot?
那個該死的瘋子追上我們嗎  多多
- Okay, okay. - That's right.
-好吧  好吧  -沒錯
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Thank you.
-嗯嗯嗯  -謝謝
Yep, right, right, right.
好吧好吧
Hi, we just need to borrow this.
我們想借一下這個
Over my dead...
除非從我...
body.
尸體上跨過
Yeah, that, that exactly, yes, um...
對  那就是尸體
Uh, that's good enough, right?
這樣就行了吧
Yup.
對
So sorry, we're gonna take really good care of it.
抱歉  我們會妥善使用的
Thanks so much.
非常感謝
Nice to meet you.
很高興認識你
Hey, I know homelessness is a complex issue
我知道流浪漢問題非常復雜
that can't be solved by charity alone,
不能僅僅靠慈善機構
so I, uh, I hope this helps the situation just a little.
所以我希望這能幫你改善一下情況
Sorry, man.
抱歉  伙計
Thank you.
謝謝
God bless you.
上帝保佑你
Jack, come on!
杰克  走了
You're very calm
你很冷靜
for someone who's just lost
雖然剛剛丟失了
the bodily evidence that he's a murderer.
自己殺人的證據
Yes, remind me how that happened again.
對  跟我說說怎么會丟的
This might come in handy.
這可能會有用
Just doing what you said.
根據你說得
New evidence, new culprits,
新的證據  新的犯人
new narrative, right?
新的手法  對吧
Could you...
你能...
could you just take that jumpsuit off?
你能脫掉這身連體衣嗎
- Wait, what, out here? - Yes, yes.
-等等  在這里嗎  -沒錯
We need somebody to help us, you guys.
我們需要找人幫忙  伙計們
We're trying to be discreet, okay,
我們要格外小心  好嗎
and he can see you from a mile off with that, so...
他在一英里外就能看到你這身衣服  所以...
I could be naked under this.
我底下可能什么都沒穿的
Is that discreet?
這算格外小心嗎
Hey, dude,
哥們
why are you texting me right now?
你為什么現在給我發信息
I'm not, I don't have my phone.
我沒有  我連手機都沒帶
Then what's...
那怎么...
Oh no.
不
Alan?
艾倫
Wait, is that the cop?
等等  是那個警察嗎
Oh shit.
該死
Dude, he has your fucking phone.
哥們  你的手機在他手上
That's bad, right?
這不大妙  對吧
Wait, I don't get it, why is...
等等  我不明白  為什么...
I--I don't know,
我不知道
but I feel like that can't be good.
但我感覺這不是好事
There's, like, emojis.
這還有  表情
Are you kidding me?
你在開玩笑嗎
He is framing us, hello!
他在陷害我們  拜托
Fuck!
操
- Fuck, fuck! - Shit!
-操  操  -該死
That's exactly what he's doing.
他就是想這么挫
Fuck me!
操
Oh God, oh my God.
天啊  天啊
Fucking be kidding me.
開什么玩笑
Fuck my life, shit!
真操蛋
Okay, this can't be happening right now.
不可能是這樣的
He doesn't know where we are.
他不知道我們在哪里  對吧
- That's true. - Right?
-沒錯  -對吧
That's a good point.
好主意
We can ditch the dead guy
我們可以直接扔掉這個死人
and just go our separate ways.
然后就此分道揚鑣
We can leave it anywhere.
我們可以隨便丟在哪里
No, that is not a good idea.
不  那不是什么好主意
He killed Nick, and you stomped on this fucking guy's head.
他殺了尼克  你還踩了這個家伙的頭
I am not the one
這個瘋子
who fuckin' brought that lunatic into my house.
可不是我請到我家的
Okay, that costume was amazing.
好吧  那套裝扮真是太棒了
- It wasn't a costume! - It wasn't a costume!
-那不是裝扮  -那不是裝扮
Oh my God, oh my God, it was Halloween!
天啊  天啊  這是萬圣節
How was I supposed to know?
我怎么知道
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
哥們  哥們  哥們
Okay, that dead cop
那個死掉的警察
took my name, man.
記了我的名字  伙計
He radioed in about us.
他用無線電匯報了我們
You know why?
你知道為什么嗎
Because you're always throwing your name around.
因為你天天到處丟你的名字
Oh, look, you dropped something.
看  你丟了點東西
Your fuckin' name.
是你的名字
Oh, yeah, that's my fault.
對  變成我的錯了
That's on me, okay.
都怪我  好吧
Oh yeah, it is.
沒錯
You know what?
你知道嗎
Good luck with it.
祝你好運
I'm fuckin' done.
我受夠了
- I'm out. - You're done?
-我不干了  -你不干了
Oh, you're gonna go?
你要走嗎
You're gonna walk away from here?
你準備就這么離開嗎
Oh, this is really something coming from you.
你的主意還真是不錯
Hey, by the way, quick question.
順便  快問快答
How you doin' with the very first problem
你這輩子第一次遇到
in your entire life
不能用錢解決的問題
that you couldn't just throw money at, huh?
感覺怎么樣
You didn't mind my money
你在抽我毒品時
when you were hooverin' up my fuckin' drugs, right?
對我的錢可沒有意見
Oh yeah,
沒錯
and you were pitchin' me
你還給我推薦
your stupid fuckin' apps.
你那個愚蠢的應用
My stupid fucking apps?
我愚蠢的應用
Shut the fuck up,
閉嘴
both of you, oh my God!
你們倆都一樣  天啊
Nick, Nick is dead in your studio.
尼克  尼克死在你的工作室
The cop, dead in your garage.
警察  死在你的車庫
There's photos on both of your phones.
你們倆的手機上都有照片
All right, maybe if...
好吧  也許如果
maybe if we just give the body back,
也許如果我們把尸體還回去
and I'll say sorry.
我去道個歉
Oh, wake up!
醒醒
We know nothing about this guy.
我們對那家伙一點都不了解
He has our names, your address.
他知道我們的名字  你的地址
I mean, Alan gave him his fucking résumé.
我是說  艾倫幾乎給了他他的簡歷
Okay, we don't need to keep putting each other down, you guys.
我們不需要一直互相揭短吧  伙計們
Okay, that psycho, he wore gloves.
那個瘋子戴著手套
Our prints are all over it.
上面全是我們的指紋
He's gonna kill us
不管我們手上
whether or not we have this thing.
有沒有這玩意  他都會殺了我們
It's a person.
這是一個人
Fuck all that noise, okay?
別說廢話了  好嗎
And the cops, when the cops come looking for us,
警察  等警察來找我們
they're gonna shoot me,
他們會朝我開槍
and then he's gonna lock you both up.
然后他會把你們全關起來
Do you want to risk that,
你們想冒這個險嗎
is that what you want to do?
你們想這么做嗎
What the fuck do we do?
我們該怎么辦
We make it go away.
我們把它處理掉
No body, no evidence.
沒有尸體  就沒有證據
We gotta bleach him.
我們要用漂白劑
Pulverize the teeth.
磨掉他的牙齒
Burn off the fingerprints.
燒掉指紋
We disfigure the face.
毀掉他的臉
We melt him down.
把他融了
We drain the blood and the bodily fluids.
放干血和體液
We mix those with bleach.
和漂白劑混在一起
We also bleach the inside.
體內也要使用漂白劑
We chop him into pieces small enough
把他切成很小的塊塊
that they can't be recognized as human
這樣就算有人找到了部分殘渣
in case somebody finds one of 'em.
也根本認不出這是人
Vinegar to soften the bones.
用醋酸軟化骨頭
We put each part in a different plastic bag,
用不同的塑料袋分裝各個部位
fill 'em with lye, tie the tops, and we bury them
用堿液裝滿  系緊  然后每袋都
as far away from each other as possible.
埋得越遠越好
Uh, that is why you're single.
所以你才單身
Oh, okay.
好吧
I'm the only one of us that watched Breaking Bad?
只有我一個人看過《絕命毒師》嗎
Are you kidding me?
你們在開玩笑嗎
That show redefined television.
那部劇簡直是重新定義了"電視劇"
Okay, uh...
好吧
where exactly are we meant to do all this?
我們要去哪兒干這些事
I don't know, but you know what?
我不知道  但你知道嗎
Not here, so let's...let's just go.
反正不在這里  所以我們...我們走吧
Let's go, yeah.
走吧
Oh, okay, no, I'll get it.
行吧  不  那我來推吧
Thanks, guys, thanks for all of your help.
謝了  多謝你們的幫助
Appreciate it.
非常感激
You dumb dicks.
你們這些蠢蛋
Son of a bitch.
混蛋
Why do you have a gun?
你為什么會有槍
Why wouldn't I?
為什么沒有
What if I go to the movies
萬一我去看電影
or my local Planned Parenthood
或者進行節育
and some asshole comes in with a gun to shoot everyone?
然后沖進來一個拿槍的混蛋開始掃射呢
Nobody would've gotten hurt tonight
要是人人都帶錢
if everybody had a gun.
今晚根本不會有人受傷
I work long hours,
我會工作到很晚
I go running early.
清晨去跑步
It makes me feel safer.
這讓我更有安全感
Have you ever had to use it?
你曾經被迫用過嗎
I just killed two people right in front of you.
我剛剛在你面前殺了兩個人
I know, who's gonna be next?
我知道  下一個是誰
You're not grasping the reality of what I'm saying.
你沒有理解我說的話的含義
I kill people.
我殺人
You haven't killed me.
你還沒殺我
Come on.
走吧
Let's get you cleaned up.
先把你身上弄干凈
*No one knows who I am*
*沒人知道我是誰*
*Nobody recognizes me*
*沒人認出我*
*No one knows who I'm supposed to be*
*沒人知道我該是誰*
*For Halloween*
*萬圣節*
Dalmore neat, and a slightly burnt, perfect,
純達爾摩  以及一杯略濃的
Sipsmith and Cokey martini,
斯皮史密斯和科基馬蒂尼
straight up with a twist,
用扭吸管和
12 year Coal Ila for the scotch.
12年的原桶威士忌
What?
怎么了
A drink order shouldn't have 25 words in it.
點酒不該超過25個字
Look at these two.
看那兩個人
Hold that for a sec.
稍等一下
Uh, I'm gonna go...
我得先去...
take care of this.
處理一下
That booth when you get back.
回來后去那個卡座
*This year for Halloween*
*今年的萬圣節*
*I'll just be me*
*我只想做我自己*
Thank you.
謝謝
Maggie, what are you doing?
瑪姬  你在做什么
Is this crazy?
這太瘋狂了吧
No.
不
You don't meet guys like this every day.
這種人不是隨便就能碰到的
He's...he's smart, he's strong,
他很聰明  他很強大
he's employed.
他受雇的
He can handle you.
他能駕馭你
Timing's a bit off, but that's okay.
時機有點不對  不過沒關系
Grow through conflict.
通過沖突成長
Yeah, yeah, this is it.
你割我砍 五金和電鋸
All right, what now?
那現在怎么辦
Uh, well, padlock is shit,
鎖很破了
and we need what's in there, so.
我們需要里面的東西  所以
Never paid for a bike in my life.
這輩子騎的自行車都沒花過錢
Okay, let's do this.
好吧  來吧
So this doesn't feel like much of a plan.
這一切好像并不在你計劃之內
You said you could track him with a computer.
你說你能用電腦追蹤到他
Can you get into this?
你能黑進這臺嗎
I'm a data engineer, not a hacker.
我是數據工程師  不是黑客
Yes.
可以
Just take me a minute to get around this guy's password.
給我點時間繞過這家伙的密碼
I'm gonna find those assholes for you.
我會為你找到這些混蛋
What?
什么
Is this everything?
全拿齊了嗎
I guess we're about to find out.
到時候就知道了
Seriously?
認真的嗎
Don't deny me this, Dorothy.
別再挑我毛病了  多蘿西
Tonight isn't really what I was expecting, okay?
今晚已經超出我的想象了
So, yeah,
所以沒錯
I want a machete.
我要一把大砍刀
All right.
好吧
It says we start with the face.
劇里說應該從臉開始
I still can't believe it's him.
我還是不敢相信就是他
I know.
我知道
Doesn't he have like 20 million Twitter followers?
他在推特上不是有兩千萬粉絲嗎
Not anymore.
現在沒了
Okay.
好吧
I'm in.
我進去了
You can track pretty much anybody's smartphone
你現在可以追蹤任何人的智能手機了
as long as a single one of their apps
只要他們手機的后臺
has live location in the background.
有運行一個程序
Code's running.
代碼在跑了
So I gotta say,
我不得不說
seeing you do what you do,
看到你做事
hearing you talk.
聽你說話
Suddenly so much makes sense.
突然一切感覺都說得通了
How?
為什么
I'll answer one of yours
你回答我一個問題
for each one you answer of mine.
我就也回答你一個問題
Come on.
來嘛
All the secrets, the deceptions.
所有的秘密和欺騙
You must be dying to just talk straight to someone.
你肯定很想找人說說心里話吧
Why are you here?
你為什么要來這里
Because I wanna be.
因為我想來
Why?
為什么
My turn.
輪到我了
Who paid you?
誰雇的你
I don't know.
我不知道
I never meet him.
我從來沒見過他
Do you know what the dark web is?
你知道暗網是什么嗎
Yes.
知道
The part of the internet that's encrypted and untraceable...
加密不可追蹤的網絡
where you would go if you want someone killed.
想殺人的話就上那個網
It's one of the many places you can go to do that, yes.
的確是可供選擇的平臺之一  沒錯
The visible world is so bright and reassuring,
我們肉眼可見的世界過于光明美好
but it needs the dark.
但總是需要黑暗的
The man who pays me owns the dark.
雇我的人擁有黑暗
You don't know him, he doesn't know you.
你不認識他  他不認識你
You get paid in electronic currency.
他用電子貨幣付款
Completely anonymous.
完全匿名
How much did you get for the guy in the bag?
你殺死袋子里的人能得到多少酬勞
More than anyone, ever.
比任何目標  都多
And I thought you were hot
我還以為你只是長得帥
before I knew you were rich.
沒想到還很有錢
Your turn.
輪到你了
Do you know why I like Halloween, Maggie?
你知道我為什么喜歡萬圣節嗎  瑪姬
The candy?
糖果
People.
人類
They wear masks their whole lives,
他們這輩子都戴著面具
pretending that life has meaning.
假裝生命有意義
When you kill somebody,
當你設了人
all of that's gone.
這一切都會化為泡影
Halloween is the closest people come to admitting
萬圣節是人類最接近于承認
that we are defined by death.
我們由死亡定義的時刻
How do you come to do what you do?
你怎么會做這一行
Choose a job you love,
選了自己喜愛的職業
you never have to work a day in your life.
下輩子都不用工作了
I want that choice.
我也想擁有這個選擇
Life carries most people along.
人總是生不由己
So much happens,
很多事
so little is made to happen.
根本沒有意義
But life is consequence.
但人生都是有后果的
You throw a glass, it breaks.
你丟下一個玻璃杯  杯子會碎
You cut someone, they bleed.
你劃傷別人  他們會流血
You kill someone, they're gone.
你殺人  他們就死了
I was always taught that consequences are to be feared.
我總是被教導要敬畏后果
Every decision I make,
我做的每個決定
every second of my life
我生命中的每一刻
is based on what someone else wants or needs,
都是基于別人想要什么  需要什么
it's like a fucking straitjacket.
就像一團垃圾
And then there's you,
然后你出現了
saying consequences are proof of power.
你說后果只是權力的證明
You can do anything you want.
你想做什么都行
All of it's good, do it.
放手去做
Because none of it means anything.
因為一切都沒有意義
Was it hard
第一次
to kill someone the first time?
殺人難嗎
Maggie...
瑪姬
None of it's hard.
什么都不難
Dead cops aren't good for business.
死警察對交易可不利
Find them.
找到他們
There was a complication.
出了點狀況
Small.
小狀況
So?
所以呢
So nothing.
所以沒什么
I've got it under control.
一切都在我掌控中
This isn't like you, Wilkes.
這不像你  威爾克斯
One complicated night in a decade
十幾年來第一晚出點狀況
isn't a bad track record.
不能算壞記錄
I hope you know where my body is.
我希望你知道我的尸體在哪里
You're watching me.
你在監視我
Maybe.
也許
On and off.
偶爾吧
That wasn't part of the deal.
協議中可沒寫這一條
Neither is lying to me.
也沒寫你可以向我撒謊
Even great white sharks have their predators, Wilkes.
大白鯊也有天敵  威爾克斯
Two hours.
兩小時
Sort your mess out.
解決你的麻煩
Don't let me down.
別讓我失望
Fuck me!
操
Don't touch your face, Jack.
別噴你的臉  杰克
It's basically acid.
那幾乎是純酸
Okay.
好的
What's next?
接下來呢
Burn off his fingerprints.
燒掉他的指紋
You, it's your turn.
你  輪到你了
Now.
快點
Okay.
好吧
Oh, shit.
該死
The skin is coming off!
皮膚掉下來了
- Oh, God. - Fuck, ahh!
-天啊  -操
Okay, ahh!
好吧
Oh, fuck.
操
He's leaking.
他滲水了
He's leaking, he's leaking. Okay.
他滲水了  他滲水了  好吧
Oh, God. Oh, God.
天啊  天啊
Why isn't Alan doing any of this gross shit, huh?
為什么艾倫不用干這種惡心的活
He's the one that got us into this mess.
明明是他給我們捅的簍子
Hey! One of us has to keep our eye
總得有人
on the bigger picture, okay?
掌控全局
I will look up the instructions,
我負責看步驟
and you two carry them out.
你們倆負責實施
Thank you.
謝謝
Chop, chop.
快點
We need to find that body, now.
我們得趕緊找到那具尸體
You said "We."
你說"我們"
Okay, this is them.
好了  找到他們了
They're at a hardware store 10 blocks from here.
他們在十個街區外的五金店
Alan is doing a Google search.
艾倫在搜索
Trying to destroy a body,
看起來他好像是想
by the looks of it.
毀掉一具尸體
Now I can tap into any camera in the area
現在我可以進入那個區域內任何
with a built-in sensor or actuator.
有內置傳感器或驅動的攝像頭
There they are.
找到他們了
Is this live?
這是實時的嗎
It was 10 minutes ago.
這是十分鐘前
If I connect Alan and Jack using Find My Friends,
如果我用"找到我的朋友"聯接艾倫和杰克
we can track them with Jack's phone.
我們就能用杰克的手機找到他們
Body cam footage is instantly uploaded to a cloud server.
隨身攝像頭錄像會實時上傳到云服務器
Can you access that server?
你能連接到服務器嗎
It'll be traceable to this computer.
那這臺電腦也能被追蹤到
I'm okay with that.
我不介意
Me too.
我也是
Find the video we're in and delete it.
找到有我們的錄像并刪除
We should send it to them.
我們應該發給他們
We've already sent the photos.
我們已經把照片發過去了
Let's have a little fun.
來找點樂子吧
Hey, Officer.
警官
Trick or treat, motherfucker.
不給糖就搗蛋  混蛋
Yeah, what's up, boy?
你們好啊  伙計
You guys look great.
你們看上去棒極了
Dunder Mifflin for the win!
敦德·米福必勝
Oh, shit.
該死
Oh, shit, get over here.
該死  過來
Guys.
伙計們
Look, we have a dead body here.
聽著  我們有一具尸體
We need your help.
我們需要你的幫助
Someone has been murdered.
有人死了
Okay, okay, it's gettin' away from us here.
好吧  越扯越遠了
This isn't what it looks like, Officer.
我知道這看上去不大妙  警官
Just listen to me, my name is Alan Morgan Adams.
聽我說  我叫艾倫·摩根·亞當斯
What is this guy's problem?
這家伙到底什么毛病
Oh, my God!
天啊
Oh, my God, oh my God.
天啊  天啊
- What do we do? - Focus, focus, focus.
-我們怎么辦  -冷靜  冷靜
No, what do we do, what do we do?
不  我們怎么辦  我們怎么辦
There is no footage of us killing the cop
沒有我們殺死那警察的證據
because we didn't actually do it.
因為不是我們干的
He's just trying to freak us out.
他只是想嚇唬我們
He's trying to make us crack,
他想讓我們崩潰
that is all he's doing.
這就是他的把戲
- Oh, my God. - Yeah, well, it's working.
-天啊  -成功了
I'm cracked.
我崩潰了
Alan, I need you to log on to Jack's Apple account,
艾倫  我需要你連接到杰克的蘋果賬號
Find My iPhone,
找到我的手機
and then delete all the messages.
然后刪除所有的信息
That's it.
就這樣
Wait, how do I do any of that?
等等  我要怎么做到這些事
Are you kidding me?
你開什么玩笑
You do it then, Jack!
那你來  杰克
- I don't know how! - Exactly!
-我不知道怎么做  -沒錯
I pay nerds to do that for me.
這些事我都是雇書呆幫我做的
All right?
好嗎
Maggie.
瑪姬
Maggie's helping him.
瑪姬在協助他
Oh, wait, the blonde that was with him tonight?
等等  今晚和他一起的金發女郎嗎
Yeah, the one that was dressed as, um...
對  就是那個穿得像
uh, Elsa from Frozen.
《冰雪女王》里的艾爾莎一樣
Marie Antoinette, you dipshit!
法國艷后  你這個白癡
Do you know anything about anything
你腦子里面除了有動畫片
that's not been made into an action figure?
還能有點別的東西嗎
I'm so sorry, professor.
很抱歉  教授
I'm not an expert in Civil War history, okay?
我不是文明戰爭歷史的專家
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait,
等等  等等
hold on, you guys, it says here
等等  伙計們  這上面說
the lye is gonna take like hours to work.
堿液需要作用好幾個小時
Oh, shit. We have to heat it
該死  我們得加熱到
to almost a thousand degrees?
將近1000度
You didn't think to tell us that before we started?
你不會在我們開始之前告訴我們嗎
You could've looked it up your fucking self, Dot!
你自己不會看嗎  多多
Call me Dot one more fucking time.
再叫我多多試試
What you gonna do?
你想怎樣
- Do something. - I surrender and I let go,
-來啊  -我投降不計較
I surrender and I let go.
我投降不計較
Do that.
隨你吧
It says here we could also
這上面說我們還可以
burn the entire body, that would work.
燒毀整具尸體  那樣也行
What website are you on?
你到底在看什么網
Wikipedia.
維基百科
What?
什么
Okay, you know what,
你知道嗎
it's not as if we can start a fire in here anyway, so.
反正我們也不可能在這里點火
Oh, yeah, actually, never mind
沒錯  其實不重要
because it has to be hot enough
因為火焰溫度也得高到
to turn him into ash,
能將他燒成灰
not just a bubbly stew person.
而不是只會給他燒的起泡泡
That's great.
太棒了
So...
那...
Hospitals, clinics, mortuaries,
醫院  診所  停尸間
they...they have incinerators.
他們有焚化爐
My mom, she used to work at a hospital,
我媽媽  她曾經在醫院工作
and they'd also discard
他們也會燒掉
like the old placentas and the foreskins and stuff,
割下來的包皮或者胎盤之類的東西
they burn them at the end of the night.
他們會在晚上下夜班后燒
Right, right, right, right, right, okay.
對對對  好吧
I can work with that.
這樣也行
Is the real world too gory for you, Monster Maker?
現實世界對你來說是不是太殘酷了  怪獸制造者
Yes.
是的
Yes, it is, actually.
其實還真是
- That's the whole point. - Hold on.
-你說對了  -等等
Would a funeral home work?
殯儀館行嗎
There's one on Hooper Street.
胡珀街有一家
Yes, yeah, that's perfect.
可以  太棒了
Uh, I don't know about that, Dot.
我可不敢確定  多多
Rothy.
蘿西
Uh, think about it.
好好想想
We already broke into this building.
我們已經闖入了這個地方
Now you want us to break into other buildings?
現在你們還想闖下個地方
There's...there's more bodies.
去個有更多尸體的地方
Yes!
沒錯
The faster that we feed this fucker to the incinerator,
我們越早把這玩意送進焚化爐
the faster that this is done.
就能越早完事
We take your trust fund money,
我們用你的信托基金
we buy plane tickets to Jamaica,
買機票去牙買加
and we spend the rest of our miserable year drinking mojitos
喝著雞尾酒  在沙灘上3p
and having threesomes on the beach.
度過今年的悲慘時光
Okay, yeah.
好吧
Lead us to a funeral home.
帶我們去殯儀館
Clear your browser history,
清除瀏覽器記錄
put him back in the cart.
把他搬回購物車上
You, clean this shit up.
你把這里收拾干凈
You know neither one of us
你知道我們倆
is gonna be in that threesome, right?
都不會參與3p的吧
Yeah, I know.
我知道
- Now! - Yeah, okay.
-快點  -好的
Ah, shit, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
該死  該死  該死
Come on, let's cut through here.
從這邊抄近道
Can you hurry up?
你能快點嗎
I don't understand you,
我真是無法理解你
but I feel like you might be the first person I've met
但是我感覺你可能是我長久以來
in a very long time...
遇到的第一個
that understands me.
理解我的人
After you kill them,
你殺了他們后
after tonight,
今晚過后
you can teach me some things.
你可以教我一些東西
I can teach you some things.
我可以教你一些東西
We can be together,
我們可以一起
just the two of us,
就我們倆
doing anything we want.
想做什么都行
There is no "We."
沒有"我們"
This is it.
到了
Let's do this.
進去吧
Can I help you, ma'am?
有什么需要幫助的嗎  女士
Um, hi, yes,
你好  是的
we need your help.
我們需要幫助
We have a dead body, and there's this guy,
我們有一具尸體  有一個人
and he's trying to kill us--
她想要幫助我們
Please press the button
請在說話前
before speaking, ma'am.
按按鈕  女士
Oh, my God!
天啊
We have a dead body, someone is trying to kill us.
我們有一具尸體  有人想殺了我們
Open the fucking door!
趕緊把門打開
Come, come.
快點快點
Is that--
那是...
Yeah, yes, yes.
沒錯  沒錯
Well, shit.
該死
Where are his goddamn teeth?
他的牙齒在哪里
Oh, my God, why does everyone keep pulling guns on us?
天啊  為什么所有人都要朝我們拔槍
We don't got time for this, all right?
我們沒時間耗了  好嗎
He's gonna kill us.
他會殺了我們
Who?
誰
Oh, shit, I knew that was gonna happen!
該死  我就知道會這樣
- Get in! - I'm coming!
-進來  -我來了
No. No.
不  不
No!
不
I'm sorry, guys.
對不起  伙計們
I can't fuckin' do this.
我不行了
I am out!
我不干了
What?
什么
Come back, you asshole!
回來  你這個混蛋
Jack! Fuck!
杰克  操
Okay.
好吧
- Where'd he go? - I don't know.
-他去哪里了  -我不知道
God, what is my deal?
天啊  我怎么了
I'm sorry, Dorothy.
對不起  多蘿西
I'm sorry I got us into this.
對不起我把我們卷進來
I'm sorry I'm always up in everyone's face,
對不起  我總是惹大家煩
I'm always pressuring people into doing shit.
我總是逼大家做各種事
I'm sorry I can never stop running my fucking mouth.
對不起我的嘴巴永遠停不下來
Calm down, it's fine.
冷靜點  沒事的
Um, what the--
你...
what the fuck are you doing?
你他媽干什么呢
Somebody's trying to kill us right now.
有人正想殺了我們呢
- Are you-- - Right, no, I--
-你  -對  不  我...
Fuck you. Go.
滾吧  趕緊去
Go to the incinerator please.
趕緊去焚化爐
Yeah, okay.
好吧
Wait, what am I supposed to do once I find it?
等等  我找到后該干什么
It's an oven, Alan.
那是個爐子  艾倫
Do you know how to turn on an oven?
你知道怎么打開爐子嗎
Okay.
好吧
Where the fuck are you?
你在哪里呢
Fuck.
操
Good luck getting in here.
祝你能進來
Shit.
該死
What is wrong with you?
你怎么回事
Keep it together.
振作點
You fuckin' pussy.
你這個慫炮
You got this.
你可以的
Jack!
杰克
Alan!
艾倫
Seriously, that's all you have?
說真的  你只有一塊木板嗎
It was all I could find, Dorothy.
我只找到了這個  多蘿西
Oh, my God, you scared the shit outta me.
天啊  你真是把我嚇了一跳
Is this it, this is it?
是這個嗎  是這個嗎
Yeah, it's gonna take a minute to heat up.
是的  加熱需要一分鐘
We don't have a minute, Alan.
我們沒有一分鐘了  艾倫
The son of a bitch is in the building.
那混蛋就在樓里
- What? - Yeah.
-什么  -沒錯
Are you serious?
你是認真的嗎
It has to get to like 1400 degrees or it's not gonna work.
必須得加熱到1000多度  不然沒用的
Oh, my God.
天啊
Oh, my God, we're gonna die tonight.
天啊  我們今晚死定了
We're gonna die tonight.
我們今晚死定了
We're gonna fucking die tonight.
我們今晚絕對要死了
No, no, okay, don't check out on me now.
不  好吧  別煩我
Just get this thing going,
趕緊把這個搞定
I have an idea.
我有個主意
Oh, fuck.
操
Shit.
該死
Please, God.
上帝啊
Please let me live.
讓我今晚活下來吧
Please, little sweet baby Jesus.
拜托  親愛的小耶穌
I'll give all my money to kids.
我把我的錢都捐給小孩
I promise.
我保證
I'll live my life like it's Christmas every day.
我會將每天都當做圣誕節般度過
I'll live my life in the past, the present, and the future.
我過去  現在和未來的每一天都會好好度過
I will never do any drugs,
我不會吸毒
and I won't disrespect women.
不會輕視女性
Oh please, sweet Jesus, let me live.
拜托  親愛的耶穌  讓我活下來吧
Okay, okay.
好吧  好吧
No, no!
不  不
Shit.
該死
Don't worry.
別擔心
I'm just gonna take the body,
我只是來拿走尸體
and then you can go home.
然后你就能回家
I'm sor--
對不...
I am so sorry,
我很抱歉
I really did think I could do that with a straight face there.
我真的以為我可以面無表情地說出來的
Where's the girl?
那女孩在哪里
Okay.
好吧
Careful now.
小心點
You don't want to miss me
你可不想不小心打歪了
and hit your boyfriend there.
打中你的男朋友
Fucking shoot him!
開槍打死他
Fucking hold him still!
你抓穩他
Fuck!
操
Find the goddamn gun!
趕緊找槍
I can't reach it!
我夠不到
I got it.
我撿到了
This is what death looks like, boy.
這就是死亡的模樣  孩子
I hope that one drink was worth it.
我希望那一杯酒值得
How does death look now, asshole?
現在死亡看上去怎么樣  混蛋
Jesus Christ.
上帝啊
I only asked you to deliver him.
我只要你把他帶過來
You said you wanted to make a statement.
你說你想確認一下
There's your statement.
我給你確認
The money is transferred.
錢轉過去了
I trust if you're satisfied
我相信你很滿意
we can put tonight's... difficulties behind us.
我們可以將今晚的...意外  拋諸腦后
Have all the complications been dealt with?
所有情況都處理了嗎
No loose ends.
沒有活口
You hear that BS?
你聽聽這鬼話
The phone is dead.
手機關機了
Even the phone is dead!
連手機都關機了
I killed you.
我明明殺了你
Hell is empty,
地獄空蕩蕩
and all the devils are here.
惡魔在人間
I just wanted a little bit of what you had.
我只是想擁有一點你擁有的東西
But I'm a fast learner.
但我學得很快
Stabbing me wasn't very nice.
捅我可不地道
Maggie!
瑪姬
But can I tell you a secret?
但是我能告訴你一個秘密嗎
I'm so happy to be rid of any delusions.
我很樂意擺脫各種幻想
No, no.
不  不
Costume.
裝扮
Amazeballs.
牛逼